Alex Terreros



PROFILE

I have been passionate about computers since childhood and am highly dedicated to achieving my goals. I previously worked in a research group at my university, where I gained valuable experience in research and software development.

CONTACT

@ ale_dario_04@hotmail.es \$\pi + (593)96-320-1396

- My website
- ORCID

⊠ Quito, Ecuador

PERSONAL INFORMATION

Citizen: Ecuadorian

Languages: **Spanish** (Native)

English (B2)

SKILLS

- Python, R, SQL, C++
- VueJS, NodeJS, Angular
- · Latex, Word, Excel
- · Linux, Git, Docker

EXPERIENCE

TECHNICAL SUPPORT at Consejo de Gobierno del Régimen Especial de Galápagos Febr 2018 - Mzo 2018

JUNIOR DEVELOPER at Ine4cElectronics Oct 2022 - Mzo 2023

JUNIOR DEVELOPER at VivaBox Oct 2023 - Aug 2024

RESEARCH ASSISTANT at IDEIAGEOCA Research Group, Salesian Polytechnic University

Mzo 2023 - Sept 2024

EDUCATION

HIGH SCHOOL CERTIFICATE IN COMPUTER APPLICATION SERVICES Unidad Educativa Fiscomisional San Francisco de Asís, Galapagos Islands - Ecuador. **2013–2019**

ENGINEERING IN COMPUTER SCIENCE Salesian Polytechnic University, Quito - Ecuador. **2020–2024**

COURSES AND CERTIFICATIONS

COURSE PROGRAMMING IN C++. Udemy. Certificate	2020
INTRODUCTION TO PYTHON. Coursera. Certificate	2020
INTRODUCTION TO THE CYBERSECURITY. Cisco. Certificate	2021
PYTHON 3 COURSE <i>Udemy</i> . Certificate	2024
ARTIFICIAL INTELLIGENCE AND DEEP LEARNING IN PYTHON Udemy.	2024
CERTIFICATION LE-1: LINUX ESSENTIALS. LPI. Certificate	2024
ENGLISH COURSE. University of Victoria, Canada.	2024
CERTIFIED CLOUD PRACTITIONER. AWS.	Act.

PUBLICATIONS

FACIAL ETHNICITY IDENTIFICATION BY COLLABORATIVE VOTING SYSTEM CDVE2024, Lecture Notes in Computer Science, Springer, Valencia, Spain, September 15-18, 2024.

EXAMS AS A SERVICE: SYNERGIES BETWEEN CHATGPT, AND CLOUD COMPUTING FOR EDUCATION (IN PRESS) SmartTech-IC 2024, Communications in Computer and Information Science (CCIS) series, Quito, Ecuador, December 2-4, 2024.